

Abdurrahmangazi Mah. Sancaktepe İSTANBUL

+90 506 391 73 19 📞

kivanc@hltkvnc.com

linkedin.com/halitkivancbozdag in

/hltkvnc

## **EXPERIENCE**



2019-... **Digital Marketing Manager** 

Sodexo Avantaj ve Ödüllendirme

l'm responsible for all Digital Marketing Actions (SEM, SEO, Social Media, Content Marketing, Email Marketing etc.)

2017-2019 Online Sales Senior Executive

Sompo Sigorta

I was leading to Online Sales Project and also responsible for Online Sales Performance, Digital Paid Channels and SEO.

2015-2017 **Digital Marketing Senior Executive** 

Eureko Sigorta

I was leading to Online Sales Project and also responsible for Online Sales Performance and Digital Paid Channels.

2010-2015 **Digital Marketing Executive** 

VakıfBank

I was responsible for Digital Paid Media Management (Search,Social Media and Display Media) and website management.

#### **EDUCATION**



2004-2009 Hacettepe University

Public Administration and Political Science

1995-2003 Gölbaşı Anatolian High School

### **REFERENCE**

İlker Arabacı

**Umut Erişen** 

CTO, Eureko Sigorta AMETA Regional Sales Director, Sodexo

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am from Ankara, born and raised. I am married and have a child. I have been working in the field of digital marketing for about eleven years. I love researching and learning about all the technologies and solutions relevant to my job. My hobbies include Amateur Radio (TA2HKB), Quantum Physics and cycling.

### **FOLLOW ME**

Github: github.com/hltkvnc

Instagram: instagram.com/hltkvnc

Twitter: twitter.com/hltkvnc

Linkedin: /halitkivancbozdag

#### **PROFESSIONAL**

ANALYTICS

DIGITAL ADS

CONTENT MARK.

TEAM MNG.

# **PERSONAL**

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

AFTER EFFECTS

HTML

JAVASCRIPT

PYTHON